foreign
and I am a proud Prudential client today
I'm here to share with you some tips on
how to set up a standing order like a
pro I'm doing this so you do not forget
or miss making any of your premium
payments
now first things first if your agent is
helping you with the process make sure
that they have the correct account
information
you don't want your premiums going to
the wrong place
with a bank
that your bank name
and most importantly your policy number
are accurate that way Prudential knows
exactly who you are and what accounts to
apply the payments to
don't forget to add the correct amount
that you want to be deducted you don't
want any surprises yeah lastly share a
copy of your standing order with
Prudential or your agent that way they
can double check that everything is in
order and you can rest easy knowing your
premiums are being paid on time
now please set up your standing order
and live your best life knowing that
Prudential Uganda is facing life with
you
[Music]
Prudential let's listen live together
turinawi